A Guide to the Charles F. Gillette, Papers, ca. 1880-1985 (bulk 1918-1969)
Library of Virginia
- Client Correspondence and Card File, 1921-1968.
  - Renard, Mrs. Wallace- CCN 682 1942 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 697
  - Reynolds, David P.- CCN 683 1958-1965 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2219
  - Reynolds, J. Louis- CCN 684 1947 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 864
  - Reynolds, Mrs.J. Sargent- CCN 685 1962-1966 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2397
  - Reynolds, Richard- CCN 688 1944-1949 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 641
  - Reynolds, Richard (Cemetery Plot)- CCN 690 1962 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2111
  - Reynolds, Mrs. Richard S., Jr. (see also Walker, Bradford CCN 1114)- CCN 687 1956-1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 447
  - Reynolds, Richard S., Jr.- CCN 687 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds, Richard S., Jr.- CCN 687 1962-1965 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Reynolds, Mrs.Richard S., Jr.- CCN 1134 1953-1954 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 208
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2059
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1957 Jan (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1957 Feb (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1957 Mar-Apr (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1957 May-Aug (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1957 Spt-Dec (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1958 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds Metals, - CCN 686 1959-1966, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Rhoads, Webster, Jr.- CCN 691 1946-1948 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 485
  - Richardson, Mrs.Enos- CCN 692 1954-1955 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Richardson, F. L. W.- CCN 693 1967 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2488
  - Richardson, Richard C.- CCN 694 1944 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Richberg, Donald R.- CCN 695 1954 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Richman, Dr. Donald W.- CCN 696 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2459
  - Richmond Beautification Committee, - CCN 697 1949-1950 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Civic Center, - CCN 698 1960-1963 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2293
  - Richmond College, - CCN 956 n.d. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 43
  - Richmond Memorial Hospital, - CCN 699 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Richmond Professional Institute, - CCN 700 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2305
  - Ridge Drive-In Theatre, - CCN 701 1950 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 985
  - River Road Baptist Church, - CCN 703 1965 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - River Road Subdivision, - CCN 704 1955 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2075
  - Riverside & Dan River Cotton Mills, - CCN 705 1942-1951 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Rixey, James Barbour- CCN 706 1953 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1150
  - Roanoke Public Library, - CCN 707 1950-1954 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 974
  - Roanoke Rapids Cemetery, - CCN 708 1947 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Robbins, Marvin R.- CCN 709 1943-1957 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 443
  - Robertson, Archibald G.- CCN 1178 1942-1967 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 645
  - Robertson, Mrs.Walter S.- CCN 711 1941-1957 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 501
  - Rochelle, I. F.- CCN 712 1950-1958 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 1001
  - Rocky Mount Cord Co., - CCN 713 1942 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 732
  - Rocky Mount High School, - CCN 714 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1174
  - Rocky Mount Methodist Church, - CCN 715 1959 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2254
  - Rocky Mount Mills, - CCN 716 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 723
  - Rogers, Mrs.Carey- CCN 719 1964 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2411
  - Rose, W. H.- CCN 718 1962 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Rosen, R. Wallace- CCN 717 1954-1956 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2050
  - Royster, Dr. Thomas S.- CCN 721 1953-1955 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 1151
  - Royster, Mrs. William S.- CCN 720 1963 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 2379
  - Ruddock, Mrs.Billings E.- CCN 722 1944-1945 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Ruddick, Margaret Patterson- CCN 723 n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Russell, Emerson C.- CCN 724 1965 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2445
  - S General, 1942-1952 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - S General, 1953-1968 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - St. Anne's School, - CCN 725 1955 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2071
  - St. Augustine's College, - CCN 726 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2355
  - St. Bridget's Catholic Church, - CCN 727 1950-1954 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 992
  - St. Christopher's School, - CCN 728 1959 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 711
  - St. Gertrude's School, - CCN 1091 n.d. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 1190
  - St. James Church, Wilmington, NC, - CCN 729 1947 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2377
  - St. John's Church- Park, - CCN 730 1962 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - St. Louis Country Day School, - CCN 731 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - St. Luke's Church Restoration, - CCN 732 1955-1956 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2100
  - St. Mary's College, - CCN 734 1944-1945 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 791
  - St. Mary's College, - CCN 734 1946 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - St. Mary's College, - CCN 734 1947-1957 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - St. Matthew's Episcopal Church, - CCN 733 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2162
  - St. Michael's Episcopal Church, Colonial Heights, VA, - CCN 1170 1958 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2225
  - St. Michael's Episcopal Church, Raleigh, NC, - CCN 735 1957 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - St. Paul's Church, Edenton, NC, - CCN 737 1952 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1098
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church, - CCN 736 1960-1962 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2297
  - St. Stephen's Episcopal Church, - CCN 738 1951-1966 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 284
  - St. Thomas Church, - CCN 739 1947-1961 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2288
  - Samples, P. Franklin- CCN 740 1959-1965 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Samuels, Joseph S. & Sons, - CCN 741 1955-1957 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Saunders, E. A., Jr.- CCN 996 n.d. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 46
  - Schaum, Mrs. Norborne M.- CCN 742 1938-1954 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 581
  - Schaum, Mrs.Norborne M.- CCN 742 1955-1966 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Schenck, Hollis- CCN 1158 n.d. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 604
  - Schwartzchild, Gus M., Jr.- CCN 743 1948-1952 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 984
  - Scott, Mrs.Frederick- CCN 744 1946-1959 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 689
  - Scott, Mrs.Marian DuPont ("Montpelier")- CCN 745 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 459
  - Scott, Mrs.Pearson- CCN 1231 1956 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2132
  - Scott, William H. (Cemetery Plot)- CCN 746 1958 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2189
  - Seaboard Passenger Station, - CCN 747 1945 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Seward, William R.- CCN 748 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2168
  - Shackelford, Willis- CCN 749 1948-1950 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 895
  - Shaw, W. W.- CCN 750 1947 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Sheltering Arms Hospital, - CCN 751 1964-1967 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2425
  - Shelton House, - CCN 752 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2227
  - Sheppard, Dr.L. Benjamin- CCN 755 1949-1950 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 945
  - Sheppard Memorial Hospital, - CCN 753 1954-1957 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Showalter, Dr. H. B.- CCN 754 1946-1948 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Siegel, John B., Jr.- CCN 756 1958 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2229
  - Simmons, John B.- CCN 757 1964 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2402
  - Simmons, Kenneth B.- CCN 759 1961 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Simon, Frank A.- CCN 758 1944 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Sitterding, William- CCN 1212 1929 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 363
  - Skinner, Mrs.Frank L.- CCN 760 1947 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 954
  - Smith, Alton B.- CCN 762 1957 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2186
  - Smith, Mrs.Benjamin- CCN 763 1923-1951 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 181
  - Smith, Mrs. Eldridge- CCN 761 1957-1965 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1111
  - Smith, H. Laurie- CCN 765 1946 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Mrs.H. McKay- CCN 766 1946-1955 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 259
  - Smith, Mrs.James H.- CCN 767 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 1074
  - Smith, John W.- CCN 768 1963-1957 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2371
  - Smith, Lee- CCN 769 1958-1960 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Mrs.P. R.- CCN 770 1952-1967 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 2127
  - Smith, Wiley- CCN 771 1956-1959 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 2134
  - Smith-Douglas Co., - CCN 764 1954-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2022
  - Southampton Memorial Hospital, - CCN 773 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2296
  - Southampton Memorial Hospital, - CCN 773 1962-1966 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Speasmaker, Mrs. Herbert B.- CCN 772 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2479
  - Spencer, Mrs.M. C.- CCN 774 1943 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Spessard, Rutherford- CCN 775 1944-1945 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 754
  - Spicer Mill Farm- House No.1, - CCN 972 n.d. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2002
  - Spicer Mill Farm- House No.2, - CCN 975 n.d. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2004
  - Sprigg, Mrs. James C., Jr.- CCN 776 1960 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Sproul, H. B., Jr.- CCN 777 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2101
  - Sprunt, J. Laurence- CCN 778 1954 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2025
  - Stallard, Mrs. Beecher- CCN 779 1965 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2439
  - Stanley, Thomas B.- CCN 780 1948-1962 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 919
  - Starke, Mrs. Thomas J.- CCN 781 1947-1952 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 872
  - State Capital Life Insurance, - CCN 782 1944-1949 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 920
  - State Planters Bank, Richmond, VA, Broad Street, - CCN 783 1949 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 923
  - Stensland, T. N.- CCN 784 1955 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Stephens, Robert L.- CCN 785 1962-1966 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2361
  - Stettinius, Wallace- CCN 786 1966-1968 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2421
  - Stevens, Hugo- CCN 787 1947-1962 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 846
  - Stewart Estates ("Brookhill"), - CCN 968 1957 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2147
  - Stonewall Jackson Hospital, - CCN 789 1953 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 1170
  - Stranahan, Mrs. F. D.- CCN 790 1941-1945 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 519
  - Stranahan, Mrs. F. D.- CCN 790 1946-1949 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Stranahan, Mrs. F. D.- CCN 790 1950-1956 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Street, W. R.- CCN 1032 n.d. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2446
  - Suburban Bank, Richmond, VA, Broad Street Road, - CCN 1083 n.d. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2263
  - Suggs, William D. (Chesterfield Ave.)- CCN 791 1951 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 978
  - Suggs, William D. (Gratton Rd.)- CCN 792 1965 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2452
  - Suiter, D. L.- CCN 793 1952 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 990
  - Sunnyside Presbyterian Home, - CCN 794 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2316
  - Suntide Motel, - CCN 795 1958 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2197
  - Sutton, Frederick I.- CCN 796 1950-1952 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 876
  - Sweet Briar College, - CCN 797 1960-1964 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 361
  - Sydnor, Mrs. Eugene B., Jr.- CCN 798 1952-1954 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 1064
  - Sydnor, W. D.- CCN 799 1947-1951 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Sylvania Industrial Corp., - CCN 800 1942-1955 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 719
  - Sylvester, Mrs.N.- CCN 801 1951-1952 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 1055
  - T General, 1944-1967 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Taft, E. Hoover, Jr.- CCN 954 1949-1968 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 950
  - Taft, Mrs.William H.- CCN 1232 1952 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Taliaferro, Mrs. T. B.- CCN 1233 1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Tanner, Elam, L., Jr.- CCN 1234 1948-1950 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 910
  - Tanner, W. R.- CCN 1235 1945 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 787
  - Tasman, Mrs. Harry G.- CCN 1236 1953-1959 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Henry- CCN 1237 1959 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2259
  - Taylor, J. P. (Meadow Farm)- CCN 989 1947-1960 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 393
  - Taylor, J. P. (Cemetery Plot)- CCN 1092 n.d. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 1138
  - Taylor, Jacquelin E.- CCN 1239 1957-1967 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Taylor, Mrs.S. W.- CCN 981 1955-1956 Jun (Box 65, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2093
  - Taylor, Mrs.S. W.- CCN 981 1956 Jly-Dec (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Taylor, Mrs.S. W.- CCN 981 1957-1964 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Thalhimer, Charles G.- CCN 984 1955-1964 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2021
  - Thalhimer, William B., Jr.- CCN 1240 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 994
  - Thomas, Mrs.Harold E.- CCN 1241 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2046
  - Thomas, Wilton L.- CCN 1108 n.d. (Box 65, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 735
  - Thompson, Alfred C.- CCN 1242 1948-1949 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 915
  - Thompson, Mrs.Thomas P.- CCN 1243 1945-1957 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Thompson, Dr.William T.- CCN 1244 1950-1957 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 952
  - Thorington Construction Co., - CCN 1245 1950-1951 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 1026
  - Thornton, Dr.W. S.- CCN 1246 1962-1968 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 2359
  - Thorpe, A. P.- CCN 802 1945-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 544
  - Thorpe, Dr.Adam T.- CCN 803 1949-1955 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Timberlake, Wayt B.- CCN 804 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2001
  - Todd, G. Carroll- CCN 805 1942-1946 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 545
  - Toler, W. Henry- CCN 806 1943-1948 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Tompkins, Mrs.[unknown]- CCN 1238 1958 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Toms, Zach- CCN 807 1952-1956 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1093
  - Toms, Mrs.Zach- CCN 808 1942 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 685
  - Towers, Thomas R.- CCN 809 1965 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2448
  - Trapnell, William H.- CCN 810 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2389
  - Trice, Franklin A.- CCN 811 1950 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1008
  - Trigg, William R., Jr.- CCN 812 1953 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Trinity Church, Charlotte, NC, - CCN 813 1959 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Truslow, Hansford B.- CCN 814 1952 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Tucker, Beverley- CCN 815 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2252
  - Tucker, Charles A.- CCN 816 1942-1949 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 745
  - Tupper, Mrs. T. C.- CCN 817 1945-1947 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 805
  - Tyson, Jewel W.- CCN 818 1945-1954 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 772
  - Tyson, Robert C.- CCN 819 1965-1966 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2467
  - Tyson, Robert C.- CCN 819 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - U General, 1946-1960 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Underwood, W. B.- CCN 820 1964 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2394
  - Union Theological Seminary, - CCN 822 1942-1965 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 717
  - Unionville School, - CCN 821 1956 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2131
  - Universal Leaf Tobacco Co., - CCN 823 1954-1966 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1186
  - University of Illinois- Dept. of Landscape Architecture, - CCN 824 1949 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - University of North Carolina, - CCN 825 1957 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - University of Richmond (See also Richmond College), - CCN 826 1955-1965 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - University of Virginia, - CCN 827 1944-1948 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Uzzle, Mrs. D. W., Jr.- CCN 828 1957 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2142
  - V General, 1943-1968 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Vaden, Dr. Edwin B.- CCN 829 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2116
  - Valentine, Charles- CCN 830 1948 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 860
  - Valentine, Mrs.Granville Gray- CCN 831 1943-1952 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1108
  - Van Clief, Mrs. Courtland- CCN 832 1942-1966 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 743
  - van Straaten, Harry J.- CCN 833 1948-1958 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 917
  - van Straaten, Harry J.- CCN 833 1960-1963 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Vaughan, W. C.- CCN 835 1959 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Vaughn, D. C.- CCN 834 1965 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2442
  - Vauter's Church, Essex Co., VA, - CCN 983 n.d. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2048
  - Venters, Mrs. W. Victor- CCN 836 1955-1959 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2253
  - Veterans Hospital, - CCN 837 1945-1946 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Vick, Dr. Clyde W., Jr.- CCN 1031 n.d. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2340
  - Virginia Association of Workers for the Blind, - CCN 838 1964 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2399
  - Virginia Baptist Building, - CCN 839 1962 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2307
  - Virginia Baptist Home for the Aged, - CCN 840 1950 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 976
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Hampton, VA, - CCN 841 1956 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2102
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co., Norfolk, VA, - CCN 842 1955 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2056
  - Virginia Employment Commission, - CCN 843 1962 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2352
  - Virginia Historical Society, - CCN 844 1948 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 421
  - Virginia Historical Society - Jamestown Church, - CCN 845 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Hot Springs, Inc., - CCN 846 1957 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2144
  - Virginia Military Institute (Cocke Memorial), - CCN 1142 1938 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 623
  - Virginia Outdoor Advertising, - CCN 847 1956 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Presidents Garden, - CCN 848 1941 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 703
  - Virginia Presidents Garden, - CCN 848 1942 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Presidents Garden, - CCN 848 1943 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Presidents Garden, - CCN 848 1944 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Presidents Garden, - CCN 848 1945-1946 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Virginia State College, - CCN 849 1938-1956 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 599
  - Virginia State College- Norfolk Division, - CCN 850 1956 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 935
  - Virginia Tractor Company, - CCN 851 1948 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 899
  - Virginia Trust Company, Richmond, VA, Malvern Avenue Branch, - CCN 852 1955-1965 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2083
  - Virginia Union University, - CCN 853 1942-1968 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 747
  - von Gontard, Mrs. Adalbert- CCN 854 1946-1951 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 870
  - W General, 1942-1942 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Walker, Bradford H.- CCN 855 1965-1966 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2457
  - Walker, Frank S., Jr.- CCN 856 1961 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2357
  - Walker, H. Ross- CCN 857 1951-1955 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 237
  - Walker, John Scott- CCN 858 1951-1952 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Walker, Mrs.Joseph G.- CCN 859 1944 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Mrs.Samuel G. (Cemetery)- CCN 860 1942-1942 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 730
  - Walker, Dr.Thomas- CCN 861 1955-1957 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2079
  - Walker, William L.- CCN 862 1954-1955 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2024
  - Wall, Garrett B.- CCN 863 1956 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Wallace, Robert L.- CCN 864 n.d. (Box 70, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 883
  - Walston, D. Stuart- CCN 865 1954-1957 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2015
  - Walston, D. Stuart- CCN 1068 n.d. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2165
  - Warwick Branch Bank, Newport News, VA, - CCN 866 1953 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1178
  - Washington & Lee University, - CCN 867 1944-1963 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 460
  - Waterman, William W.- CCN 868 1950-1965 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 991
  - Watkins, F. P.- CCN 869 1961 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2313
  - Watkins, Lucie Lornez (Estate)- CCN 870 1961 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Watson, R. P.- CCN 1247 1948-1949 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 909
  - Watson, Van- CCN 872 1949 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Way, Dr.Joseph H.- CCN 873 1963-1964 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 2334
  - Wayne Memorial Hospital, - CCN 874 1953-1954 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 1146
  - Webb, Dr.Alexander- CCN 875 1946-1953 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 820
  - Webb, Clinton- CCN 1185 1957-1968 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2213
  - Weddell, Alexander- CCN 876 1938-1942 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 300
  - Weddell, Alexander- CCN 876 1943-1948 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Weddell, Mrs.Alexander (Cemetery Plot)- CCN 877 1933-1948 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 448
  - Weddell, Mrs.Alexander (Hill Top Cottage)- CCN 878 1946-1947 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 107
  - Weeks, Mrs.George L.- CCN 879 1951 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Weidmann, Ernest- CCN 880 1947 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 837
  - Weil, Herman- CCN 881 1950-1965 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 531
  - Weinberg, Joseph- CCN 882 1949-1950 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 966
  - Welch, John L.- CCN 883 1950-1967 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2466
  - Wescott, G. Wise- CCN 974 n.d. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2114
  - West, Caleb D., Jr.- CCN 884 1954-1955 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - West Avenue Improvement Association, - CCN 885 1960 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - West Haven Presbyterian Church, - CCN 888 1955-1956 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 971